是啊
Yeah, you're right.
我们急诊室的人不过就是在救命
In ER, we're only saving lives.
捞不到名声 没有
There's no fame, there's no, uh,
CNN来采访
-CNN interviews. -(LAUGHS DRYLY)
那我只能继续用尼克了
I guess I'll just have to stick with Nic.
等等
Whoa, wait a minute.
你们不是...你俩没...
You're not... You guys aren't...
什么
What?
上床吧 抱歉 我以为我厌恶的口气能暗示我的意思了
Sleeping together? Sorry, I thought that was implicit in my disgust.
其实非常明显
Explicit, actually.
没有 我有绝对不能跟同事约会的规矩
No, I have a very strict rule against dating colleagues.
是吗
Oh, really?
我称之为"斯特兰奇准则"
I call it the "Strange Policy."
太棒了 很高兴有东西是以我命名的
Oh, well, good, I'm glad something's named after me.
我发明了一种椎板切除术手术
I invented a Iaminectomy procedure.
似乎没人愿意管它叫斯特兰奇术
And yet, somehow no one seems to want to call it the "Strange Technique."
是我们一起发明了那个术式
We invented that technique.